Suraj Duwal

Summary

A self-motivated, friendly and hardworking with 1.8 year of experience working in Website development in laravel framework. Able to communicate effectively with a team and very keen to develop more professional skills. Good knowledge of the creation of Web design software and programming languages relevant to the website.

Employment History

Internship

Allure Private Limited 06/2018 - 09/2018

- Collaborated with various teammates when working on day-to-day tasks and devising new concepts.
- Learn about the laravel framework and done project on it
- Learn about Wordpress and done project on it

Web developer Trainee

View Nepal 10/2018 - 01/2019

- Gained Experience of real life project.
- Done an academic dyanic website through laravel. This website have been lived under the name www.novel.edu.np

Full stack developer

Momtech 01/2019 - 04/2019

- Get used to with the website design and development.
- Done Various project and improved the web designing skill and development

Laravel developer

E-signature 06/2019 - Present

- Web application development
- Develop API
- Work on real life Web Application and Web Devlopment Projects

Professional Skills

- Laravel
- Git
- Jquery

- Html , Css , Bootstrap
- MySQL
- API

Education

Bachelor's Degree

Kathmandu University Graduated

11/2018

+2 Science

Khwopa Higher Secondary School

......

SLC

Wiseland English Secondary School

Graduated 05/2012

Projects

1.Business continuity application

A web application developed with laravel

2. Novel Academy

Developed a academic dynamic website known as novel academy.

Link of Website: http://www.novel.edu.np

3. Developed many other dynamic websites.